Guide to the Richard Bonelli Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Scores
  - Collection of English songs II (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Covers inscribed: Richard Bonelli. Collection reflects original order. Contains published scores and manuscripts. Bacon, Ernst, 1898-, Buffalo Gals. (New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., c1946) -- Bantock, Granville, Sir, 1868-1946. Songs from the Chinese poets, 3rd ser. Feast of lanterns. (New York: Galaxy Music Corp., c1918) -- Berger, Jean, 1909-, Sonnets. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1942) -- Brahe, May H. (May Hannah), 1885-1956. Bless this house. (New York: Boosey & Hawkes, Inc., c1932) -- Bridge, Frank, 1879-1941. Isobel. (London: Chappell & Co. LTD., c1913) -- Campbell - Tipton. Sea Lyrics. Crying of Water. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1912, copy 1 p.3-6 only, annotated, copy 2 complete, unannotated); Sea Lyrics. Crying Water. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1914) -- Clay, Frederic. Gipsy John. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1898) -- Coates, Eric, 1886-1957. Bird songs at eventide. (New York: Chappell - Harms, Inc., c1926); I heard you singing. (London: Chappell - Harms, Inc., c1923) -- Coningsby Clarke, Robert. Blind Ploughman. (London: Chappell & Co. LTD., c1913) -- Cowen, Frederic H. (Frederic Hymen), Sir, 1852-1935. Border Ballad. (New York: Boosey & Co., c1895) -- Crist, Bainbridge, 1883-1969. Chinese Mother Goose Rhymes. (New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., c1917) -- Damrosch, Walter, 1862-1950. Danny Deever. (Cincinnati: John Church Co., c1897); Death and general Putnam. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1936) -- Del Riego, Teresa, 1876-1968. Homing. (New York: Chappell - Harms, Inc., c1917) -- Dobson, Tom, 1890-1918. At the edge of the sea. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1920) -- Duke, John. Calvary. (New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., c1948) -- Dunhill, Thomas F. (Thomas Frederick), 1877-1946. Wind among the reeds. Cloths of heaven. (London: Stainer & Bell, LTD., c1911) -- Dunn, James Philip, 1884-1936. The bitterness of love. (New York: J. Fischer & Bro., c1915) -- Giannini, Vittorio, 1903-1966. Heart Cry. (New York: G. Ricordi & Co., Inc. c1929) -- Golde, Walter, 1887-1963. Garden of tomorrow. (manuscript) -- Granier, Jules. Hosanna! Easter Song. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1891) -- Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907. Digte af Otto Benzon, op. 69. Gynger en bååd på bølge. (New York: Carl Fischer) -- Hadley, Henry Kimball, 1871-1937. Beautiful mother. (New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., c1921) -- Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966. Songs. Charity. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1890); Christmas Eve. (New York: Galaxy Music Corp., c1936); Dawn shall over lethe break. (Paris: Winthrop Rogers, c1934); Do not go, my love. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1917); Donkey. (Paris: Winthrop Rogers, c1934); Donkey. (New York: Boosey & Co., Inc., c1934); Joyful Song. (Boston: G. Schirmer, c1920) -- Hampson, Gordon. Death. (manuscript) -- Hardelot, Guy d', 1858-1936. Because. (Melbourne: Chappell & Co. LTD., c1912) -- Harrhy, Edith. Colette. (New York: Boosey & Co., Inc., c1930) -- Horsman, Edward, 1873-1918. Bird of the wilderness. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1915); Songs of old China. Yellow Dusk. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1916) -- Huhn, Bruno. Invictus song. (Boston: The Arthur P. Schmidt Co., c1910) -- Kellog, Kay. Give me a ship and a song. (manuscript) -- Kramer, Walter A. Songs. At the evening's end. (New York: J. Fischer & Bro., c1931); I have seen dawn. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1922) -- Smith, Harry Bache, 1860-1936. Robin Hood. Brown October ale. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1891) -- Spier, Harry R. (Harry Reginald). Indian Serenade. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1924) -- Taylor, Deems, 1885-1966. Captain Stratton's Fancy. (New York: J. Fischer & Bro., c1923) -- Wagenaar, Bernard, 1894-1971. Songs. Dusk. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1926); Songs. I stood in dreams of darkness. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1926); Songs. May-night. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1926) -- Whiting, Arthur. Fuzzy - Wuzzy. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1901) -- Whithorne, Emerson, 1884-1958. Across the fields to Anne. (New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, c1941) -- Wolfe, Jacques, 1896-1973. Johnny Appleseed. (New York: Carl Fsicher, Inc., c1946) -- Wragg, Russel, 1899-, Hearth Song. (Cincinnati: The Willis Music Co. c1936) -- Wrightson, Herbert J. (Herbert James), 1869-1949. Drake's drum. (New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., c1924) -- trad. French folk song. Allons gay, gayement, ma mignone. (New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, c1943) --
  - Collection of English songs III (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Covers inscribed: Music. Collection reflects original order. Contains published scores and manuscripts. Bainbridge, Crist. Would you go so soon? (New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., c1923) -- Balogh, Ernö, 1897-, Within my heart. (New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, c1938); Within my heart. (manuscript) -- Campbell-Tipton, Louis, 1877-1921. Jester Songs. Fool's soliloquy. (New York: G. Schirmer, c1912) -- Giannini, Vittorio, 1903-1966. Tell me, oh blue, blue sky. (New York: G. Ricordi & Co., Inc., c1927); Waiting. (New York: G. Ricordi & Co., Inc., c1935) -- Grainger, Percy Aldridge, 1882-1961. Twa Corbies. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1929) -- Griffes, Charles Tomlinson, 1884-1920. Poems by John Masefield. Old song re-sung. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1920) -- Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966. Voices. (New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, c1943) -- Haun, Ewald. Songs. (New York: G. Ricordi & C., c1933) -- Hayes, Roland, 1887-1977. Water boy. Negro convict song. (Boston: Winthrop Rogers, LTD., c1922) -- Holmès, Augusta Mary Anne, 1847-1903. Au Pays. Warrior returns. (New York: Carl Fischer, c1945) -- Holst, Gustav, 1874-1934. Hymns from the Rig Veda, op. 24, No.1-3. (London: J. & W. Chester LTD., c1920); Hymns from the Rig Veda, op. 24, No.4-6. (London: J. & W. Chester LTD., c1920) -- Hutchinson, Victor Hely, 1901-1947. Who goes home? (London: Elkin & Co. LTD., c1933) -- Kramer, Walter A. Souls. (Seelen). (New York: Galaxy Music Corp., c1935) -- Sanderson, William. Time to go. A Shanty ballad. (New York: Boosey & Co., Inc., c1927) -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc) -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. You. Words and Vocal adaptation by Bainbridge Crist. (New York: Carl Fischer, c1946) -- Scott, Cyril, 1879-1970. Unforeseen. (New York: G. Ricordi & Co., c1911) -- Sjöberg, Carl-Erik, 1935-, Visions (Tonerna). (New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, c1937); Visions (Tonerna). (manuscript) -- Squire, W. H. For Jack. (New York: Chappell - Harms, Inc., c1904) -- Templeton, Alec, 1910-1963. When whisp'ring strains. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1937); Wi' a hundred pipers. (New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., c1937) -- Walton, Kenneth, 1904-1986. Tang of the sea. (New York: Chappell - Harms Inc., c1933); You and I. (New York: Sprague-Coleman, c1937) -- Woodforde-Finden, Amy, 1860-1919. Indian love lyrics. Temple Bells. (New York: Boosey & Co., LTD., c1902)
  - Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907. Peer Gynt (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Alceste (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Sommernachtstraum (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1916-1933 (Othertype 26, Folder 1)
  - 1921-1947 (loose pages) (Othertype 26, Folder 2)
  - 1932-33 (Othertype 26, Folder 3)
  - 1933-1935 (Othertype 26, Folder 4)
  - 1936-1939 (Othertype 27, Folder 5)
  - 1939-1953 (Othertype 28, Folder 6)
  - 1885-1916 on Mrs. Perry Davis and Mr. Modini (Othertype 28, Folder 7)
- Publications
  - Music Academy of the West 1947-1949. Slides #1-75 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Includes two sheets of machine -typed captions for slides.
  - Music Academy of the West 1947-1949. Slides #76-150 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Music Academy of the West 1947-1949. Slides #151-195 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Films
  - San Francisco Opera 1933-35 / 1937-39, 16 mm answer print. WO#: 1340 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Rehearsal for Muzio, Meisle, Pinza, Gandolfi and Bonelli; Aida. Finale of triumphal scene. Muzio, Meisle, Martinelli and Bonelli; Tristan und Isolde. Bonelli as Kurneval and Pinza as king Mark; Entr' acte callers. Augusta and Ned Harrold, Merle Preston and Dale Winter Duffy; La Boheme. Bori, Bonelli, Hardi and Borgioli; Forza del Destino. Muzio, Bonelli, Martinelli, Pinza and Gandolfi; Coq d'or. Bolm as the king and Ruiz as the princess; Tannhäuser rehearsal. The minstrel's contest in the hall of song; Tannhäuser Act II. Dress rehearsal for the chorus. Bonelli as Wolfram, Pinza as the Landgraf Gandolfi and Windheim; La Traviata. Act III, ballroom at Flora's; Lauritz Melchior and Bonelli stage an impromptu rehearsal of Otello; Aida. Martinelli as Rhadames, Coe Glade as Amneris, Bonelli as Amonasro, Rothberg as Aida; Entr' ácte. Agnini, Bonelli, Robert Miller and Windheim; Dress rehearsal with Helen Gahagan as Suor Angelica; Rigoletto. Bonelli as Rigoletto, Schipa as the duke, Emily Hardy as Gilda; Manon. Nov. 10th. with Bovy, Maison, Bonelli, Cordon and Cehanovsky; Our supper party, Nov. 17th; La Forza del Destino. Rethberg, Gigli, Bonelli.
  - San Francisco Opera 1933-35 / 1937-39, 16 mm estar dupe neg. WO#: 1340 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hanson, Howard, 1896-, Merry Mount. 1934, 16 mm answer print. P.O.#: 1570. WO#: C3XDR2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Scenes taken during dress rehearsal and subsequent performances. Act I Main street of the Puritan settlement; Act II May-day festival of the cavaliers; ACT III Brad Ford's dream: the hellish rendezvous; Richard Stokes librettist calls Mrs. Stokes; Dress rehearsal: publicity 'stills' for the newspapers.
  - Hanson, Howard, 1896-, Merry Mount. 1934, 16 mm dupe neg. P.O.#: C3XDR236170 WO#: 1570 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco Opera 1933-35 / 1937-39, NTSC VHS. Videocassette size: 7.5" x 4.25". (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Footage transfer from open reel film #1, 16mm XTER 16FPS, onto NTSC VHS. Run time: 44:15 minutes NDFTC. Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Rehearsal for Muzio, Meisle, Pinza, Gandolfi and Bonelli; Aida. Finale of triumphal scene. Muzio, Meisle, Martinelli and Bonelli; Tristan und Isolde. Bonelli as Kurneval and Pinza as king Mark; Entr' acte callers. Augusta and Ned Harrold, Merle Preston and Dale Winter Duffy; La Boheme. Bori, Bonelli, Hardi and Borgioli; Forza del Destino. Muzio, Bonelli, Martinelli, Pinza and Gandolfi; Coq d'or. Bolm as the king and Ruiz as the princess; Tannhäuser rehearsal. The minstrel's contest in the hall of song; Tannhäuser Act II. Dress rehearsal for the chorus. Bonelli as Wolfram, Pinza as the Landgraf Gandolfi and Windheim; La Traviata. Act III, ballroom at Flora's; Lauritz Melchior and Bonelli stage an impromptu rehearsal of Otello; Aida. Martinelli as Rhadames, Coe Glade as Amneris, Bonelli as Amonasro, Rothberg as Aida; Entr' ácte. Agnini, Bonelli, Robert Miller and Windheim; Dress rehearsal with Helen Gahagan as Suor Angelica; Rigoletto. Bonelli as Rigoletto, Schipa as the duke, Emily Hardy as Gilda; Manon. Nov. 10th. with Bovy, Maison, Bonelli, Cordon and Cehanovsky; Our supper party, Nov. 17th; La Forza del Destino. Rethberg, Gigli, Bonelli.
  - San Francisco Opera 1933-35 / 1937-39, NTSC BETACAMSP - 60 minute. Videocassette size: 10'' x 5.5" (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Footage transfer from open reel film #1, 16mm XTER 16FPS, onto NTSC BETACAMSP. Run time: 44:15 minutes NDFTC. Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Rehearsal for Muzio, Meisle, Pinza, Gandolfi and Bonelli; Aida. Finale of triumphal scene. Muzio, Meisle, Martinelli and Bonelli; Tristan und Isolde. Bonelli as Kurneval and Pinza as king Mark; Entr' acte callers. Augusta and Ned Harrold, Merle Preston and Dale Winter Duffy; La Boheme. Bori, Bonelli, Hardi and Borgioli; Forza del Destino. Muzio, Bonelli, Martinelli, Pinza and Gandolfi; Coq d'or. Bolm as the king and Ruiz as the princess; Tannhäuser rehearsal. The minstrel's contest in the hall of song; Tannhäuser Act II. Dress rehearsal for the chorus. Bonelli as Wolfram, Pinza as the Landgraf Gandolfi and Windheim; La Traviata. Act III, ballroom at Flora's; Lauritz Melchior and Bonelli stage an impromptu rehearsal of Otello; Aida. Martinelli as Rhadames, Coe Glade as Amneris, Bonelli as Amonasro, Rothberg as Aida; Entr' ácte. Agnini, Bonelli, Robert Miller and Windheim; Dress rehearsal with Helen Gahagan as Suor Angelica; Rigoletto. Bonelli as Rigoletto, Schipa as the duke, Emily Hardy as Gilda; Manon. Nov. 10th. with Bovy, Maison, Bonelli, Cordon and Cehanovsky; Our supper party, Nov. 17th; La Forza del Destino. Rethberg, Gigli, Bonelli.
  - Hanson, Howard, 1896-, Merry Mount., NTSC BETACAMSP - 30 minute. Videocassette size: 6" x 3 3/4" (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Footage transfer from open reel film #1, 16mm XTER 16FPS, onto NTSC BETACAMSP. Run time: 9:30 minutes NDFTC. Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Scenes taken during dress rehearsal and subsequent performances. Act I Main street of the Puritan settlement; Act II May-day festival of the cavaliers; ACT III Brad Ford's dream: the hellish rendezvous; Richard Stokes librettist calls Mrs. Stokes; Dress rehearsal: publicity 'stills' for the newspapers.
  - Hanson, Howard, 1896-, Merry Mount., NTSC VHS. Videocassette size: 7.5" x 4.25". WO#: 1570 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Footage transfer from open reel film #1, 16mm XTER 16FPS, onto NTSC VHS. Run time: 9:30 minutes NDFTC. Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Scenes taken during dress rehearsal and subsequent performances. Act I Main street of the Puritan settlement; Act II May-day festival of the cavaliers; ACT III Brad Ford's dream: the hellish rendezvous; Richard Stokes librettist calls Mrs. Stokes; Dress rehearsal: publicity 'stills' for the newspapers.
  - San Francisco Opera 1933-35 / 1937-39, Memorex DVD+R 4.7GB - 120 minutes. WO#: 5803 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Footage transfer from open reel film #1, 16mm XTER 16FPS, onto DVD. Run time: 44:15 minutes NDFTC. Black and white, silent movie with the following titles: Rehearsal for Muzio, Meisle, Pinza, Gandolfi and Bonelli; Aida. Finale of triumphal scene. Muzio, Meisle, Martinelli and Bonelli; Tristan und Isolde. Bonelli as Kurneval and Pinza as king Mark; Entr' acte callers. Augusta and Ned Harrold, Merle Preston and Dale Winter Duffy; La Boheme. Bori, Bonelli, Hardi and Borgioli; Forza del Destino. Muzio, Bonelli, Martinelli, Pinza and Gandolfi; Coq d'or. Bolm as the king and Ruiz as the princess; Tannhäuser rehearsal. The minstrel's contest in the hall of song; Tannhäuser Act II. Dress rehearsal for the chorus. Bonelli as Wolfram, Pinza as the Landgraf Gandolfi and Windheim; La Traviata. Act III, ballroom at Flora's; Lauritz Melchior and Bonelli stage an impromptu rehearsal of Otello; Aida. Martinelli as Rhadames, Coe Glade as Amneris, Bonelli as Amonasro, Rothberg as Aida; Entr' ácte. Agnini, Bonelli, Robert Miller and Windheim; Dress rehearsal with Helen Gahagan as Suor Angelica; Rigoletto. Bonelli as Rigoletto, Schipa as the duke, Emily Hardy as Gilda; Manon. Nov. 10th. with Bovy, Maison, Bonelli, Cordon and Cehanovsky; Our supper party, Nov. 17th; La Forza del Destino. Rethberg, Gigli, Bonelli.
- Sound recordings
  - Air checks 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Atwater Kent Hour, Oct. 1934; Ford Sunday Evening Hour, Dec. 1934; Chase & Sanborn Opera, 1935; Chesterfield Hour, 1935.
  - Air checks 1935 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Chesterfield Hour, Feb. - Mar. 1935.
  - Air checks 1935 - 1936 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Chesterfield Hour, Mar. - April 1935; Ford Sunday Evening, 1935; General Motors Hour, Feb. 1936.
  - Air checks 1936, 1937-38, 1943, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    General Motors Hour, Feb. 1936; Ford Sunday Evening Hour Mar. 1936, and 1937-38; Treasury Hour 1943; Home recordings 1951.
  - Air checks 1937-1940 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    With the annotation "Happy Birthday Mona!! Jan. 18, 1988."Side A: A star was his candle. Dec. 26, 1937 -- O beauty, passing beauty. Dec. 26, 1937 -- Passage bird's farewell. Aug. 1937 -- O that we two were Maying. Aug. 30, 1937 -- Without a song. Aug. 10, 1937 -- Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Porgy and Bess. It ain't necessarily so. Aug. 1937 -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar. Aug. 10, 1937 -- Old mother Hubbard -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Soirées musicales. Danza. Dec. 12, 1940.Side B: Begin in the beginning. Dec. 12, 1940 -- "Original recordings made with distant piano for orch. dubbing (1955)" -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Prologue -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern
  - Air checks 1937-1940 (duplicate) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Air checks (Box 32, Folder 7)
    With the annotation "Happy Birthday, Mona. 1987"Side A: Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen. Oct. 25, 1936 -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana. Viva il vino spumeggiante. Nov. 21, 1936 -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Hamlet. O vin, dissipe la tristesse. Nov. 21, 1936 -- Friml, Rudolf, 1879-1972. Amour-toujours-l'amour -- Wagon wheels. Sept. 18, 1936 -- Griffes, Charles Tomlinson, 1884-1920. Poems by John Masefield. Old song re-sung. Feb. 20, 1943 -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux. Sept. 21, 1941 -- I cannot sing the old songs (spoken intro.) -- Nevin, Ethelbert Woodbridge, 1862-1901. Rosary -- Fox, Oscar J., 1879-196. Hills of home.Side B: Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Romanzen und Balladen, op. 49. Beiden Grenadiere -- From Magic Music. 1941 -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Dite alla giovine. Dec. 2, 1951 -- Opera News on the Air. Dec. 12, 1953
  - Richard Bonelli discusses his career. Parts 1 & 2 of 51974 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    La Cañada, California. July 21, 1974
  - Richard Bonelli discusses his career. Parts 3 & 4 of 51974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Richard Bonelli discusses his career. Part 5 of 5. Various songs1974 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    La Cañada, California. July 21, 1974 -- Atwater Kent Hour. Oct. 15, 1934. Youmans. Through the years -- Kalman. Countess Maritza. Play Gypsie -- Hahn. Ka Barcheta -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Barnaby. Now the day is over -- Ford Sunday Evening Hour: Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive -- Westendorf. I'll take you home again Kathleen -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945. Show boat. Ol' man river
  - Opera is my hobby. The career and art of Richard BonelliJune 24, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    KANV-FM in Lawrence, Kansas with Jim Seever (sp?)
  - Miscellaneous arias and songs (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Nemico della patria -- O'Hara Jeffrey (sp?) unclear title -- Blue moon
  - Opera Guild (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Opera Guild with Dean Taylor
  - Miscellaneous arias and songs (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - A Program of old vocal records dedicated to Richard Bonelli (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Program hosted by Marti Robinson. Selections of Bonelli's opera recordings.
  - Town Hall RecitalFeb.5, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Metropolitan Opera Association. First New York Song Recital. Wolff, Ernst Victor, piano. See program (4.1.5) for content.
  - Town Hall Recital (duplicate)Feb.5, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Act 2 and Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Act 1 Oct.13, 1939; Oct. 7, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di LammermoorFeb. 3, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Metropolitan Opera. Performers: Pons, Lily, 1898-1976 as Lucia; Oliviero, Lodovico, 1886-1948 as the captain of the guards Normanno; Bonelli as Sir Henry Ashton. Lazzari, Virgilio, 1887-1953 as Lucia's bridegroom; Votipka, Thelma as her maid Alisa; Jagel, Frederick as Edgardo
  - Unidentified opera. Act 3, scene 1 and 2. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Richard Bonelli: Commercial recordings from Brunswick & Columbiaca. 1921-1940 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    Tape made from various records for Mona's birthday in 1990.Side A: Scott. Annie Laurie -- Londerry air. Would God I were the tender apple blossom -- Messager, André, 1853-1929. Bosche. Chanson Ancienne -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Serse. Ombra mai fù -- Martin. Come to the Fair! -- Sanderson. Time to go -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Luna d'estate -- Brogi. Visione Veneziana -- Kipling and Damrosch. Danny Deever -- Herbert. Fortune Teller Side B: Speaks. On the Road to Mandelay -- Flynn. Tim Rooney's at the Fightin' -- Pinsutti. Bedouin love song -- Wallace. Bohemian girl. Heart bow' d down -- Coates. Bird songs at Eventide -- Mascheroni. For all eternity -- Ross. Indian dawn -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Palms -- Yradier. Paloma -- Denza. Funiculi, Funicula
  - Elizabeth. In love with Gershwin. (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Side A: Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Embraceable you -- Foggy day -- Man I love -- Someone to watch over me -- How long has this been going on? -- I got rhythm --
  - Elizabeth. In love with Gershwin. (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Side A: Gershwin, George, 1898-1937. Embraceable you -- Foggy day -- Man I love -- Someone to watch over me -- How long has this been going on? -- I got rhythm -- Side B: Phantom of the Opera (Musical) with Guillaume, Robert.
  - Mario Chamlee. KUSC Radio Program.Sept. 3, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Opera Box. The art of tenor with Jim Sveda. Chamlee, Mario, 1892-1966. Recorded for Mona Bonelli by Arch Chamlee.
  - Petrova, M. I. (Mariia Ivanovna), soprano (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Carno, Zita, piano.
  - Templeton, Alec, 1910-1963; Ustinov, Peter; Lehrer, Tom, 1928-,Sherman - Nine tenors., Christmas morning, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    "Souvernier from the past to wish you happy birthday, 1986."
  - Great singers (Box 32, Folder 27)
    Bell Lab tests 1929-1931. Performers: Crooks, Richard, 1900-1972; Farrar, Geraldine, 1882-1967; McCormack, John, 1884-1945; Bori, Lucrezia, 1887-1960
  - Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Concerto, piano, orchestra, no. 2, op. 18, C minor May 15, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    San Diego Symphony orchestra. Wells, Howard, piano.
  - Wilson, Ernest Charles, 1896-, Unity SermonsOct. 2 - 6, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Wilson, Ernest Charles, 1896-, Unity SermonsOct. 30 - Nov. 3, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Wilson, Ernest Charles, 1896-, Unity SermonsNov.27 - Dec.1, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Wilson, Ernest Charles, 1896-, Unity SermonsJan. 8 - 12, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Wilson, Ernest Charles, 1896-, Unity SermonsJan. 29 - Feb. 2, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Wilson, Ernest Charles, 1896-, Unity SermonsFeb. 19 - 23, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Richard Bonelli air checks IV (Box 33, Folder 1)